Guide to the Michael Kahn Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Michael Kahn papers
1927-2013
1960-2013
YCAL MSS 789
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
69.79
(82 boxes) + 1 broadside folder
Correspondence, business and production files, scripts, notes, photographs, printed material, and audiovisual materials documenting Michael Kahn's career as a theater and opera director, theater administrator, and teacher of theatrical arts. Kahn's administrative and directorial work at the American Shakespeare Theatre, the McCarter Theatre, the Shakespeare Theatre, and the Juilliard School are particularly well documented.
Kahn, Michael, 1945-
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Michael Kahn, 1992-2013.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Box 32 (reel-to-reel audio recordings): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Boxes 71-73 (sound and video recordings): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Michael Kahn (1945- )
Michael Kahn was born in New York City in 1945, where he attended the High School of Performing Arts, and received a B.A. from Columbia University. He trained professionally with Michael Howard and the Actors Studio. Kahn began his career off-off-Broadway with productions including Jean-Claude van Italie's War and America Hurrah at Cafe La Mama. His Broadway credits include Showboat, Whodunnit, and The Death of Bessie Smith. Best known for directing Shakespearean plays, he has held artistic and administrative positions at theatres including the American Shakespeare Theatre in Stratford, Connecticut; McCarter Theater in Princeton, New Jersey; the Acting Company in New York City; Chautauqua Conservatory Theatre Company in Chautauqua, New York; and the Folger Shakespeare Theatre, now known as the Shakespeare Theatre, in Washington, D.C. He has directed numerous opera and regional theater productions. Kahn has also been involved in the training of professional actors through his work as a teacher and administrator at the Juilliard School, Circle in the Square Theatre School; New York University Tisch School of Arts, and Princeton University.
Scope and Contents
Correspondence, business and production files, scripts, notes, photographs, printed material, and audiovisual materials documenting Michael Kahn's career as a theater and opera director, theater administrator, and teacher of theatrical arts. Kahn's administrative and directorial work at the American Shakespeare Theatre, the McCarter Theatre, the Shakespeare Theatre, and the Juilliard School are particularly well documented.
Arrangement
Organized into five groupings: I. September 1992 Acquisition, 1947-1985. II. June 1994 Acquisition, 1927-1986. III. July 1998 Acquisition, 1943-1999. IV. January 2008 Acquisition, 1991-2006. V. June 2008 Acquisition, 1992-2004.
Material within this collection has been organized by acquisition reflecting the fact that the collection has been acquired in increments over time. Researchers should note that material within each acquisition overlaps with and/or relates to material found in other acquisitions. In order to locate all relevant material within this collection, researchers will need to consult each acquisition described in the Collection Contents section.
Researchers should also note that similar material can be arranged differently in each acquisition, depending on how the material was organized when it was received by the library.
Acting teachers -- United States; Actors -- United States; Opera -- Production and direction -- United States; Theater -- Production and direction -- United States; Theatrical producers and directors -- United States; Audiovisual materials -- United States -- 20th Century; Born digital -- United States -- 20th Century; Photographs -- United States -- 20th Century; Acting teachers -- United States; Theatrical producers and directors -- United States; Kahn, Michael, 1945-; American Shakespeare Theatre; Juilliard School; McCarter Theatre Center (Princeton, N.J.); Shakespeare Theatre (Washington, D.C.)
- September 1992 Acquisition, 1947-1985; 1; 30.71; (33 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  Consists of scripts, production files, publicity files, correspondence, photographs, and topical files documenting Michael Kahn's administrative and directorial work at the Stratford Shakespeare Theatre, the McCarter Theatre. Personal files and memorabilia are also included.
  Arrangement
  Arranged in order received.
  - Production and Administrative Files, 1959-1979
    Includes scripts, programs, set designs, correspondence and subject files, financial records, clippings, printed material and reviews.
    - Scripts, circa 1971-1979
      - "Eleanor," playscript by Arlene Stadd, undated (Box 1)
      - "The Epic of Buster Friend," film script by Richard Lenz and G. L. Blanchard, undated (Box 1)
      - "Grand Magic," playscript, undated; 2 (Box 1)
      - Romeo and Juliet, 1978 July (Box 1)
      - 'Tis Pity She's a Whore, undated (Box 1)
      - The Torch Bearers, undated (Box 1)
      - Toys in the Attic, 1978 (Box 1)
        Includes contact sheet and sales
    - Miscellaneous production materials, 1976; 5 (Box 1)
    - Films and Filming magazine, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Plays and Players magazine, 1977-1978 (Box 1)
    - Film and theater related printed material, 1977, 1979 (Box 1)
    - [Expanding File 1], 1959-1979
      - Peer Gynt, 1959 (Box 2)
      - Pericles, undated (Box 2)
      - Dialogue of the Carmelites, 1961 (Box 2)
      - Circle in the Square Theatre School, 1978 (Box 2)
      - Writers Stage Company, clippings, 1961-1962 (Box 2)
      - The Love Nest, 1960-1966 (Box 2)
      - The Funnyhouse of a Negro, 1964 (Box 2)
      - Two plays by Ionesco, 1964 (Box 2)
      - The Fantasticks, 1964 (Box 2)
      - Sunday in New York, undated (Box 2)
      - Enter Laughing, undated (Box 2)
      - That 5 a.m. Jazz, 1964 (Box 2)
      - Helen, 1964 (Box 2)
      - War, undated (Box 2)
      - America Hurrah, 1966 (Box 2)
      - The Ocean Out Front, 1965 (Box 2)
      - The Unexpected Guest, 1965 (Box 2)
      - Purple Dust, 1965 (Box 2)
      - Williamsburg Peninsula Playhouse, clipping, undated (Box 2)
      - "Miscellaneous news columns, Pre-Barnard", 1962 (Box 2)
    - [Expanding file 2], 1968-1979
      - Here's Where I Belong, 1968; 4 (Box 2)
        Includes the New York and Philladelphia productions
      - Richard II, 1968; 2 (Box 2)
      - Love's Labour's Lost, 1968; 2 (Box 2)
      - Camino Real, 1968; 2 (Box 2)
      - The Death of Bessie Smith, 1968; 2 (Box 2)
      - Juilliard, 1968-1979 (Box 2)
      - Stratford, 1969 (Box 2)
    - Publicity and reviews, 1968-1979
      Includes clippings, stage production programs, press packets, correspondence and printed publicity material.
      - Antony and Cleopatra, 1972 (Box 3)
      - The Aspern Papers, 1978 (Box 3)
      - Blues in the Night, clipping (photocopy), 1979 (Box 3)
      - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof, includes film positives for ads, 1974; 8 (Box 3)
      - The Confirmation, 1977 (Box 3)
      - Crimes of Passion, 1968; 2 (Box 3)
      - Eleanor, 1976; 2 (Box 3)
      - Grand Magic, 1978-1979 (Box 3)
      - Hamlet, 1969, 1972 (Box 3)
      - Heartbreake House, undated (Box 3)
      - Henry V, 1969; 4 (Box 3)
      - Julius Caesar, 1972; 2 (Box 3)
      - Julius Caesar, 1972, undated; 3 (Box 4)
        Includes photographs and set designs.
      - A Month in the Country, 1978 (Box 4)
      - Much Ado About Nothing, 1974-1978 (Box 4)
      - The Night of the Tribades, 1977 (Box 4)
      - No Time for Comedy, 1978 (Box 4)
      - Romeo and Juliet/Twelfth Night, 1974; 7 (Box 4)
      - "Thornhill", 1978 (Box 4)
      - Three plays by Thorton Wilder, correspondence (Box 4)
      - Three Sisters, 1969 (Box 4)
      - The Torch Bearers, 1978 (Box 4)
      - Miscellaneous clippings about the theatre, 1972-1978; 4 (Box 4)
    - Subject files, 1968-1979
      - The Acting Company, 1978 (Box 4)
      - Actors' Equity Association, 1977 March 8 (Box 4)
      - Alliance for the Development of Theatre Artists, 1978-1979 (Box 5)
      - Agents, 1974-1979; 2 (Box 5)
      - American Arts Alliance, Inc., 1978 (Box 5)
      - American Shakespeare Theatre, 1976 March 15 (Box 5)
      - Associates of McCarter Theatre Company, 1974-1979; 4 (Box 5)
      - The Association of Schools in the Arts, undated (Box 5)
      - Auditions, 1974-1978 (Box 5)
      - "Audience letters, pro and con", 1974-1979 (Box 5)
      - Awards, 1974-1976 (Box 5)
      - Barnes, Clive, 1978 (Box 5)
      - Bayer, Louise, 1974-1975 (Box 5)
      - Benefits: McCarter Theatre, 1975-1978 (Box 5)
      - Bills in the United States House of Representitives regarding The National Endowment for the Arts funding, 1975-1978 (Box 5)
      - Bookings (possible), 1975 (Box 5)
      - Brochures from McCarter Theatre, 1977-1978; 2 (Box 5)
      - Brochures, other theatres, 1976 (Box 5)
      - Brookfield Center, 1977 (Box 5)
      - Brown's Hotel, 1976 November 9 (Box 5)
      - Byrne, Governor Brendan T., 1974-1979 (Box 5)
      - Casting, 1978 (Box 5)
      - Creative Theatre Unlimited, 1974 September 25 (Box 5)
      - Critics, 1974-1979 (Box 5)
      - The Dakota, New York City, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
        Includes correspondence and papers pertaining to Kahn's apartment lease and renovation project
      - Directing Class, undated (Box 5)
      - Directors Guild of America, 1978 (Box 5)
      - Dodge Foundation, 1978-1979 (Box 5)
      - Drama seats - pricing and projection, 1975-1976 (Box 5)
      - [FEDAPT] Foundation for the Extension and Development of the American Professional Theatre, 1979 (Box 5)
      - Focus on Theatre, 1978 (Box 5)
      - Ford Foundation, 1976-1978 (Box 5)
      - Foundations - funding, 1974-1978; 2 (Box 5)
      - Frankel, Kenneth, 1976 (Box 5)
      - Fundraising - development projects, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
      - Goodman Theatre, 1975 (Box 5)
      - Goodspeed Opera House, 1978 (Box 5)
      - Grand Opera House, 1975 May 30 (Box 5)
      - The High School of Performing Arts (New York), 1977 (Box 5)
      - Hobson, Micki, 1974-1977 (Box 5)
      - House Manager, McCarter Theatre Company, 1977 December (Box 5)
      - Housing, McCarter Theatre Company, 1974 May 7 (Box 5)
      - IATSE [International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees], 1976, 1978 (Box 6)
      - Interviews, 1974-1978 (Box 6)
      - Invitations, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
      - Job Descriptions, 1974 March 18 (Box 6)
      - Kahn, Michael, 1974-1979; 6 (Box 6)
      - Kennedy Center, 1975 (Box 6)
      - League of Professional Theatre Training Programs, 1975-1978; 3 (Box 6)
      - League of Resident Theatres (LORT), 1974-1978 (Box 6)
      - Levit, Ben, 1975 (Box 6)
      - Lockwood, Bill, 1974-1978 (Box 6)
      - Lombino, Norman, 1975 (Box 6)
      - Long Day's Journey Into Night, undated (Box 6)
      - Loot, 1973-1979 (Box 6)
      - McCarter Theatre, 1971-1979
        - Correspondence and papers, 1975-1978 (Box 6)
        - Budget, 1974-1978; 4 (Box 6)
        - Box offices, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
        - Bulletins, 1977 (Box 6)
        - Calendars, 1974-1978; 2 (Box 6)
        - Capital expenditures, 1974-1979 (Box 6)
        - Communications Department, undated (Box 6)
        - Concerts Committe, 1974-1976 (Box 6)
        - Development, 1977 (Box 6)
        - Interns, 1979 (Box 6)
        - Martenson, Ed, 1976-1978 (Box 6)
        - Matchplay, undated (Box 6)
        - Mobil Foundation, 1978 (Box 6)
        - "Movies at McCarter", 1974-1978 (Box 6)
        - "Playwrights at McCarter Series", 1977-1978 (Box 6)
        - Previous productions, 1971-1975 (Box 6)
        - Priorities Committee, financial reports and correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 6)
        - Prospects, 1976-1979; 2 (Box 6)
        - Staff meetings, 1976-1979 (Box 6)
        - Subscriptions and sales, 1975-1979 (Box 6)
        - Theater personnel applicants, 1974-1978
          Employment inquiry letters. Includes resumes, reference and cover letters and letters of response by Kahn
          - Actors and actresses, 1975-1978 (Box 7)
          - Actors and directors, 1975-1976 (Box 7)
          - Assistants: administrative and directing, 1975-1978 (Box 7)
          - Choreographers, 1973, 1978 (Box 7)
          - Fight choreographers, 1974-1978 (Box 7)
          - Composers and musicians, 1975-1978 (Box 7)
          - Costume designers, 1975-1978; 2 (Box 7)
          - Stage managers and directors, 1976-1978 (Box 7)
          - Directors, 1974-1978; 3 (Box 7)
          - Lighting designers, 1975-1978 (Box 7)
          - Set designers, 1975-1978; 2 (Box 7)
          - Stage managers, 1977-1978 (Box 7)
          - General theatre positions, 1977-1978 (Box 7)
          - New playscript submissions, 1974-1978; 5 (Box 7)
            Includes "read, reviewed and returned" and "no answer to playwrights without reading," correspondence
        - Toys in the Attic, 1978 (Box 7)
        - Trustees, 1974-1979; 2 (Box 7)
      - National Endowment for the Arts, 1975-1979 (Box 8)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1975-1978 (Box 8)
      - National Theatre Conference minutes, 1977 (Box 8)
      - New Jersey Critics Association Awards, 1974-1976 (Box 8)
      - New Jersey State of Public Broadcasting Authority, 1977 (Box 8)
      - New Jersey State Council on the Arts, 1974-1978 (Box 8)
      - New Jersey State Opera, Alfredo Silipigni, 1977 (Box 8)
      - New Jersey Symphony, 1975 (Box 8)
      - Opera companies, 1978 (Box 8)
      - Paine, Pat, 1974-1975 (Box 8)
      - Paulus, Bob, 1978 (Box 8)
      - The Performance Center Theatre and School, Ltd., 1977-1979 (Box 8)
      - Performing Arts Educational Advisory Commission, 1974-1978 (Box 8)
      - PJ & B, 1974-1978 (Box 8)
      - Press correspondence, seasonal coverage, 1975-1978 (Box 8)
      - Princeton University, 1974-1978 (Box 8)
      - Princeton University Program in Theatre, 1974-1978 (Box 8)
      - Put Them All Together contract (photocopy), 1977-1978 (Box 8)
      - Ramsay, Margaret, 1974-1978 (Box 8)
      - "Reviews of Interest", 1975-1978 (Box 8)
      - Richardson, Ian, 1974-1978 (Box 8)
      - Rockefeller Foundation, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
      - "Selected Views From Professional Theatre Artists: a Report Transcribed From Taped Interviews by Dr. Louis J. Dezseran," mimeograph, 1975 (Box 8)
      - Seltzer, Dan, 1972-1978 (Box 8)
      - Seminars, 1975-1977 (Box 8)
      - Shepard, Sam, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
      - Speaking engagements, 1974-1978 (Box 8)
      - "Speech to save", 1977 (Box 8)
      - Stage production programs, 1974 (Box 8)
      - Teaching, 1975-1978 (Box 8)
      - Theatre Communications Group, 1968-1979; 6 (Box 8)
      - Triangle Club, 1975 (Box 8)
      - The Utter Glory of Morrisey Hall, 1977-1978 (Box 8)
      - The White Devil, 1979 (Box 8)
    - American Shakespeare Theatre files, 1968-1978
      - The Academy for the Performing Arts, 1976 April 2 (Box 9)
      - ACSTA [American Center for Stanislavski Theatre Art, Inc.], 1976 February 11 (Box 9)
      - American National Theatre and Academy, 1969 June 30 (Box 9)
      - Academy proposal, 1975 August 26 (Box 9)
      - Accountants Report for 1972, 1973 May 21 (Box 9)
      - American Shakespeare Festival address list, 1972 February 2 (Box 9)
      - Administrative candidate, 1973 July 6 (Box 9)
      - Advisory Board, American Shakespeare Festival, 1976 Aug 3 (Box 9)
      - Articles, printed material, 1970-1975; 2 (Box 9)
      - "Articles of rare and lasting interest", 1974-1975 (Box 9)
      - Assistant directors, 1970-1976; 3 (Box 9)
      - Audience development, 1969-1975 (Box 9)
      - Audience letters, 1973 (Box 9)
      - Audience questionaire #2, undated (Box 9)
      - Audience surveys, 1969-1975; 5 (Box 9)
      - Auditions, 1973-1975 (Box 9)
      - Behrman, S. N. "People in a Diary," printed material, undated (Box 9)
      - Benton Awards, 1970-1972 (Box 9)
      - Bicentennial, United States, 1970-1974 (Box 9)
      - Board of Trustees, American Shakespeare Theatre, memos, reports, correspondence, 1969-1976; 4 (Box 9)
      - Board of Trustees, Committees, 1973-1976 (Box 9)
      - Box office reports, 1969-1976 (Box 9)
      - University of Bridgeport, 1973-1976 (Box 9)
      - Brookfield Center, 1974-1976 (Box 9)
      - Brooklyn College School of Performing Arts, first annual Shakespeare conference, 1974 (Box 10)
      - Budget, 1969-1976 (Box 10)
      - CBS proposal, 1975 (Box 10)
      - Calendars, 1973 (Box 10)
      - Carr, Robert M., 1973-1974 (Box 10)
      - Center for Theatre Techniques in Education, 1971-1975 (Box 10)
      - Choreographers, 1973 (Box 10)
      - Community Relations, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
      - Composers, 1969-1976 (Box 10)
      - Conferences, 1976 (Box 10)
      - Connecticut Commission on the Arts, 1972-1974 (Box 10)
      - Connecticut Public Television, 1977 (Box 10)
      - Contracts, 1970-1974 (Box 10)
      - Correspondence, 1974-1977; 2 (Box 10)
      - Costumes (Brooks Van-Horne), 1971 (Box 10)
      - Designers and costumes, 1969-1977; 2 (Box 10)
      - Director of Development, 1973-1975 (Box 10)
      - Directors, 1966-1977; 4 (Box 10)
      - Directory of American Shakespeare Theatre, 1971 (Box 10)
      - Dramaturg, 1973 April 24 (Box 10)
      - Eleanor, 1976 (Box 10)
      - Equity [Actors' Equity], 1973 (Box 10)
      - FACT: First American Congress of the Theatre, 1974 (Box 10)
      - Fight director David Shemwell, 1975 May 19 (Box 10)
      - Film rentals, undated (Box 10)
      - Ford Foundation, 1971-1975 (Box 10)
      - Four year plan, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
      - Friends of the American Shakespeare Theatre, 1971-1976 (Box 10)
      - Fund Raising, 1971-1972 (Box 10)
      - "Gifted Children in the Schools" National Public Radio programs 1-5 transcripts, 1976 (Box 10)
      - Harlem Everyman Street Theatre, photographic contact sheet, 1973 (Box 10)
      - Inns and restaurants, clippings, undated (Box 10)
      - In School Program, 1973 (Box 10)
      - International Famous Agency, 1973 (Box 11)
      - Interviews wtih Michael Kahn, 1974-1976 (Box 11)
      - Invitations, 1973-1976 (Box 11)
      - Job applications, 1974-1976 (Box 11)
      - Jobs-other theatres, 1976 (Box 11)
      - Kael, Pauline, undated (Box 11)
      - Kahn, Michael personal files, 1972-1976, undated; 4 (Box 11)
      - Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, 1973 August (Box 11)
      - Landaw, Jack, "Background of the actor," typescript (photocopy), undated (Box 11)
      - League of Resident Theatres (LORT) memo, 1974 August 13 (Box 11)
      - Legislators night, 1974 (Box 11)
      - Liquor license, photocopy, 1973 February 16 (Box 11)
      - Memos, 1974-1976 (Box 11)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 11)
      - Miscellaneous press clippings, 1976-1977 (Box 11)
      - Museum exhibit, 1971-1972 (Box 11)
      - National Endowment for the Arts, 1972-1976 (Box 11)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1973-1975 (Box 11)
      - National Theatre Conference, 1972-1975 (Box 11)
      - New Play Series, 1972-1975; 2 (Box 11)
      - Noisy audience mail, 1974 (Box 11)
      - Our Town, 1975 (Box 11)
      - Performance schedule - student audience, 1968-1973 (Box 11)
      - Performing Arts Educational Advisory Commission, 1975 (Box 11)
      - Planning, 1975-1977 (Box 11)
      - Playwrights, 1970-1976; 5 (Box 11)
      - Poster from University of Hartford, correspondence, 1973 (Box 11)
      - Press, 1969-1976; 3 (Box 11)
      - Projects, 1971-1973 (Box 11)
      - Recommendations, 1976 (Box 12)
      - Requests for articles, 1971 (Box 12)
      - Residency, 1973 (Box 12)
      - Restaurants - clippings, 1972 (Box 12)
      - Reviews - other theatres, 1972 (Box 12)
      - Roberts, Meade, 1974 (Box 12)
      - Salute to Shakespeare weekend, 1973 May 15 (Box 12)
      - Schedules, 1971-1975 (Box 12)
      - Schenker, Joel, 1972-1973 (Box 12)
      - Season 1976 (Box 12)
      - Set design drawings, "Basic Scheme I" by D. W. Schmidt for The American Shakespeare Festival, Stratford, Connecticut, 1968 October 14 (Box 12)
      - Set design and ground plan, unidentified, undated (Box 12)
      - Shakespeare Institute, 1971-1976 (Box 12)
      - Shaplen, Robert, "Birth of Bangladesh," clipping, 1972 (Box 12)
      - Society of Stage Directors and Choreography, 1972-1976; 2 (Box 12)
      - Speaking engagements, 1969-1974 (Box 12)
      - Special events, 1973 (Box 12)
      - Staff meeting minutes, 1968-1974 (Box 12)
      - Stage managers, 1965, 1975 (Box 12)
      - Student productions, 1971-1973 (Box 12)
      - Subscriptions, 1971 (Box 12)
      - Theatre Communications Group, 1974-1976; 2 (Box 12)
      - Tony Van Bridge Enterprises, 1973 (Box 12)
      - "[New York]Times article," correspondence, 1971 (Box 12)
      - Tours, 1971-1976 (Box 12)
      - Training programs, 1974-1976; 2 (Box 12)
      - Twenty-fifth Anniversary Challenge Drive, 1975 (Box 12)
      - The Utter Glory of Morrisey Hall, 1977-1978 (Box 12)
      - WGBH TV "Arts Mobile", 1977 November 18 (Box 12)
      - WNET TV, 1973-1975 (Box 12)
      - Wolf, Mary Hunter, 1969-1974 (Box 12)
      - Workshops, 1971-1972; 2 (Box 12)
    - Publicity and production materials
      - All's Well that Ends Well, undated (Box 13)
      - Angel City, 1977; 2 (Box 13)
      - Antony and Cleopatra, 1972; 3 (Box 13)
      - As You Like it, 1976 (Box 13)
      - The Aspern Papers, 1978 (Box 13)
      - Awake and Sing, 1976 (Box 13)
      - Beyond the Horizon, 1974; 2 (Box 13)
      - The Confirmation, 1977 (Box 13)
      - Design for Living, 1977 (Box 13)
      - A Grave Undertaking, 1975; 2 (Box 13)
      - Hamlet, 1969 (Box 13)
      - The Heiress, 1976 (Box 13)
      - Henry V, 1971 (Box 13)
      - Hough in Blazes, 1971; 2 (Box 13)
      - Julius Caesar, 1972 (Box 13)
      - King Lear, 1975 (Box 13)
      - Kingdom of Earth, 1976 (Box 13)
      - Major Barbara, 1972; 5 (Box 13)
      - The Merry Wives of Windsor, 1971; 4 (Box 14)
      - A Month in the Country, 1978 (Box 14)
      - Mother Courage, 1975 (Box 14)
      - Mourning Becomes Electra, 1971; 5 (Box 14)
      - Much Ado About Nothing, 1969 (Box 14)
      - Night of the Tribades, 1976; 2 (Box 14)
      - No Time for Comedy, 1978 (Box 14)
      - Othello, 1970; 4 (Box 15)
      - Our Town, 1975; 4 (Box 15)
      - The Physician, 1977 (Box 15)
      - Put Them All Together, 1979 (Box 15)
      - Romeo and Juliet, 1975; 2 (Box 15)
      - The Royal Family, 1977 (Box 15)
      - Section Nine, 1975; 2 (Box 15)
      - Showboat, undated (Box 15)
      - A Streetcar Named Desire, 1976; 2 (Box 15)
      - Tartuffe, 1972; 2 (Box 16)
      - The Tempest, 1971; 2 (Box 16)
      - The Three Sisters, 1969 (Box 16)
      - 'Tis Pity She's a Whore, 1974 (Box 16)
      - The Torch Bearers [empty folder], undated (Box 16)
      - Toys in the Attic [empty folder], undated (Box 16)
      - The Utter Glory of Morrissey Hall, 1977 (Box 16)
      - A Winter's Tale, 1975; 4 (Box 16)
    - Scripts, 1971-1988
      - "Electra and Orestes", 1981; 2 (Box 16)
      - "Flux," playscript by Susan Miller, 1982 (Box 16)
      - "Frankenstein's Opening Night," playscript by Adreinne Kennedy, 1982 (Box 16)
      - "Iphegenia", undated (Box 17)
      - "Kingdom of Earth," playscript by Tennessee Williams, 1974 (Box 17)
      - The Merry Wives of Windsor, playscript and production materials, 1971; 2 (Box 17)
      - Mother Courage, undated (Box 17)
      - Peer Gynt, undated (Box 17)
      - Showboat, 1988 (Box 17)
      - "Thornhill," playscript by Meade Roberts, undated; 2 (Box 17)
      - "Traitors," playscript by Stephen Sewell, 1979 (Box 17)
      - True West, photocopy, undated (Box 17)
      - Whodunnit: A Comedy Thriller, 1982 (Box 17)